This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
[7HD Channel]
[iQIYI]
[Present]
♫Never met anyone who could make me understand this word♫
♫But when I met you, my heart started beating fast♫
♫You’re the only one in my heart who could make me feel this way♫
♫This long-awaitied moment is now over♫
♫From now on, my heart and soul will be yours for the rest of my life♫
♫Always have each other, never let go♫
♫Trust in me ‘cause I’ll be by your side♫
♫Hold my hand, Baby♫
[Desires in the Wind]
[Previously]
When everything is over, let’s go see the snow in Madelin together.
That’s the flare from the resort.
We must get out of here.
Where’s Miss Blew?
She’s been taken.
I already turned it on.
They’ll probably come swarming here soon.
Is it a trap?
I know.
But even if it’s a trap, I still have to go.
Grace, Helena is gone.
I’ll take care of her myself.
Miss Blew.
Miss Vayo.
I’m okay.
You look so much like me.
I know you’re not a bad person.
I don’t know what you’ve been through.
But your eyes, they tell me you don’t want to do this.
I can help you.
Grace is using you.
If anything happens, the first one to die is you.
It’s still not too late.
I know you don’t want to do this.
I’m sorry, Your Highness.
I just want to survive.
I don’t want to do this anymore.
If you help me, I promise I will tell Father to grant you a pardon.
I don’t think I could help you that much.
Grace’s people are guarding around this place.
Swap places with me. I’ll run away and get the police here
to arrest Grace and all the traitors.
I promise I’ll come back for you.
Just try to stall for time as best as you can.
Miss Vayo.
I’m glad you’re safe.
Miss Vayo!
Please stay with me.
- Thank you.
How’s she?
Fai just told me.
I’ve been worried sick.
Still unconcious.
Why did you have to help her run away from the hospital?
How could you let her do something dangerous like that
You know how stubborn she is.
If we didn’t help her, she would’ve found a way to escape anyway.
I don’t get it.
Why did she have to risk her life like that, all just to protect a woman–a princess?
It’s because of love.
She’s probably found someone she truly loves.
Is it even possible?
Lom and Princess Blew, do you really think it could happen?
But isn’t it something to be proud of?
Once in her life, she has sacrificed herself to protect the person she loves.
Miss Blew probably feels it too.
So, how’s Miss Blew?
How are you, my daughter?
Father.
Karel.
All traitors have been executed.
Please rest assured, Sister.
I’m such a fool to never know how much danger you had to go through.
I’m sorry I couldn’t protect you.
It’s not your fault, Father.
Thank God you’re safe.
What about Miss Vayo? Is she all right?
She’s still unconscious. But overall, she’s safe now.
For your own safety, I’ll take you back to Madelin immediately
after the doctor’s examination tomorrow.
Tomorrow…
Lom.
How are you?
I knew you all would be here.
Geez, this brat.
Where’s Miss Blew?
She just…got discharged from the hospital this morning.
Can I go see her then?
No.
You still need physical therapy.
The doctor said you can’t leave yet.
You won’t make it in time anyway.
What do you mean?
Miss Blew will fly back to Madelin this afternoon.
She came to visit you this morning but you were still unconscious.
So, she’s left you this letter instead.
By the time you are reading this letter, I would have been long gone.
I'm sorry I didn't stay to bid you farewell.
Unfortunately, a gravely ill matter of treason has required my urgent return to Madelin.
Thank you for still being alive.
Thank you...for always staying by my side and protecting me.
Thank you for getting hurt and risking your life for me.
I now realise how unconditional your love is.
It is the most precious thing in my life.
I am so blessed to be loved by the person whom I share the same feelings with.
Being apart this time, I do not know when we will meet again.
But whenever I can feel the wind blow, I will always think of you.
I love you.
May life treat you well.
I shall do my best to carry out my duty here too.
♫It’s okay, you don’t have to say it now♫
♫I want you to take your time♫
♫Those things we’ve been through♫
♫Those time we’ve spent together♫
♫I still remember them vividly♫
♫For all that we've been through♫
♫Be it good or bad♫
♫It made me realise♫
♫That having you here means so much to me♫
♫Stay with me, please don’t go♫
♫All my heart, there’s only you♫
♫Stay with me, now and forever♫
♫Let there be only me and you
♫please don’t go♫
Look after Madelin for me.
Don’t say that. You must go back to Madelin, Princess.
But for now, I want to stay here forever.
I knew it. There you are.
It’s been over a month. Your leg is as good as new now.
But the wound in your heart is probably not healed yet.
Are you coming from Surat just to annoy me?
She’s worried about you.
Hey, Uncle Thit said King Arthur has sent us an invitation to visit Madelin.
He’d like to hold a thank you party for us.
Really? I have no idea.
How would you? Secluding yourself from the world like this.
No phone calls or talking to anyone.
Yeah.
This is it, Sis. If you miss her, just go see her.
I want to, but I’m also scared.
Everything is not the same anymore.
And you chose to stay with your own fear instead?
Don’t be a chicken, Lieutenant.
You hardly blink when you fight those criminals.
Why don’t you just give it a try?
If it doesn’t work out, then you can just move on.
We’ll go with you too.
No matter what it’d turn out to be, you’ll always have us to support you.
Miss Vayo has already accepted our invitation to join the party?
Yes. Father has just received the news a while ago.
Aren’t you happy? You’ll get to see the person who saved your life.
I am.
But I’ve just been assigned a new duty.
I’m worried I mightn't be able to make preparations in time.
I understand.
After this treason matter is done, you have to prepare yourself for taking the throne.
Can you take care of the guest reception for me then?
Of course, I’ll arrange for everything and take care of the guests for you.
It’s all right.
I notice the light is still on.
Are you still working?
Yes, Father.
Seeing you like this, I’m more confident you’ll take Madelin into great prosperity–much more than when under my reign.
I could never compete with you, Father.
Would it be possible to reconsider your decision to step down from the throne, Father?
Why?
I believe you’re still in good health.
Why step down so soon?
The recent treason matter has created a wave of worry among Madelin people.
Having a new leader would help enhance the state of affairs.
Then, after I become Queen
and once Karel is ready, can I give up the throne to him?
Why would you do that?
Karel will always be there to help you anyway.
Actually, it’s not just the throne that I want to give up, but also my royal title.
Giving up royal titles is only possible when the royal member has committed a serious crime
or decided to marry a commoner.
I have absolutely no doubt you will never violate any of those rules.
What’s that matter?
Nothing, Father.
Then, never mention it to me again.
And never forget that your duty as the crown princess always comes first and foremost.
Yes, Father.
Welcome, King Arthur is waiting inside.
Please be at ease.
I hope you are well now, Miss Vayo.
Yes, Your Highness.
Isn’t Princess Catherine with you too, Your Highness?
She is engaged in her duty and won’t be able to make her presence.
But she promises she’ll join us at dinner.
You must have been exhausted from the trip.
Please get some rest and make yourself comfortable.
This way, please.
Hey, after putting our bags in the room, should we go take a walk in the garden? In case we might run into Miss Blew.
This place is so big. Even if we're in the same place–if she doesn’t want us to see her–then you won’t find her.
She must be busy. You’ll definitely see her this evening, right?
Yeah. If you two are meant to be, then it will be.
Princess Catherine will make her presence.
Please be at ease.
I’m glad to see you again, Your Highness.
Welcome to Madelin, Miss Vayo. Is there anything you find lacking here?
Prince Karel has assigned someone to take excellent care of me and my family, Your Highness.
Then, I’m relieved.
So…
Has the trip exhausted you, Miss Fah?
Not at all, Your Highness. May I ask how you are doing?
Very well, thank you.
Miss Nam, how are you doing?
I’m good, Your Highness.
I’d like to express my sincere gratitude to all of you for helping my beloved daughter.
Especially to you, Miss Vayo.
If there’s anything I could do to repay you, please don’t hesitate to say it.
Would you kindly grant me permission to make a scoop on your coronation ceremony, Your Highness?
Of course, the ceremony will be held next month.
Does that mean the princess will become Queen after that?
I’m still the same as before.
Then, on behalf of the Watinwanich family,
please allow me to take this opportunity to congratulate you in advance, Princess Blew.
No, not Princess.
It’s Queen Catherine.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
Miss Vayo, please call me like you used to.
I wouldn’t dare doing that, Your Majesty.
Because now, things are not the same anymore.
Once you become Queen, it’s time to find someone to stay by your side.
Have you given any thought to your marriage?
Or is there any prince you’ve been having your eye on lately?
I’ve hardly given it any thought, Father.
Then, do it now. What about Prince Henry? He seems to be interested in you.
Let’s not talk about this now, Father. It’d only bore our guests.
You and your family wish to move up your schedule and will return to Thailand tomorrow?
Yes, Your Highness.
Is something bothering your mind? You can be honest with me.
We’ve received outstanding hospitality at the palace, Your Highness.
My family and I are very grateful, but we’d rather not impose on you any further.
Besides, my sisters have some work to attend to.
What a pity then. Is there anything you’d like to do before you leave? I’ll have it taken care of.
I haven’t had a chance to speak with Princess Catherine since I came here, Your Highness.
I’d like to say goodbye to her before I leave.
No problem. I’ll let her know.
Karel said you want to see me.
Yes, I want to see you–
the one that’s not Princess Catherine.
I’m leaving.
I know.
In the end, we’re like a story with no happy ending.
The princess always ends up with the prince.
What happens between us, please think of it as just a dream.
It’s time to forget everything, and wake up from that dream.
Can you really forget it?
I won’t forget it.
I’ll keep it in my heart.
What can I do for us to be Wind and Phatpha again?
I’m afraid I can’t put my own happiness over my duty.
I’m obliged to my responsibilities.
I do hope you’ll live a happy life from now on.
I don’t think I can do that.
Just think of me as if I were dead.
That day when Helena died, Phatpha also left your world and would never return.
It feels like you’re breaking up with me.
I love you.
Goodbye, Princess Catherine.
I love you too, Miss Vayo.
If there’s a chance, come to Madelin again. You’re always welcome here.
Madelin is so beautiful. I will definitely come back, Your Highness.
Please come visit Thailand again if you have a chance, Your Highness. You’re more than welcome to stay at my farm.
Or at my hotel, Your Highness.
Of course, I’ll certainly be there.
We’ll take our leave then, Your Highness.
Is she still in her bedroom?
Yes, Your Highness. The princess hasn’t left her room since yesterday.
Would you like me to tell her that you’re here, Your Highness?
No need.
Since we came back from Thailand, it seems you’ve changed a lot.
How so?
It’s as if you had left your smile and happiness in Thailand.
Is it because of Miss Vayo?
What does she have to do with this?
I know you two are in love.
Watch your words, Karel.
If Father happens to hear it, he might be furious.
I need to focus on the upcoming coronation ceremony.
I don’t have time for anything nonsense.
You can lie to me but you can never fool your own heart.
I’ve never lied to my heart.
But I can’t just throw away my duty and responsibility as a crown princess.
จุดที่พี่ยืนอยู่I am standing at a point where I cannot follow my own heart.
I can’t fall in love, even when I’ve found that person I truly love.
So, you admit that you love her.
Yes, I love Miss Vayo.
Then, just follow your heart.
Ever since I can remember, you’ve always done everything for our family–
devoting yourself to the people of Madelin.
Never once have you done anything for your own needs or happiness.
So this time, I’m begging you to please listen to your heart and do something for yourself.
Even if I want to, Father will not allow it.
I never hesitate if I have to choose between the throne and the person I love.
But I don’t want to disappoint Father. I don’t want to break his heart.
Father won’t be sad or disappointed forever.
But if you make a wrong decision now, you might be sorry for the rest of your life.
Besides, Madelin still has me.
I’ll use this chance to steal the throne from you.
Thank you, Karel.
What did you just say?
You’re going to give up the throne?
Yes, Father. I’m going to give up my royal title too, for I don’t deserve to be the Queen of Madelin–
because I’m in love with a commoner.
I’m in love with Miss Vayo.
You love who?
I love Miss Vayo, Father.
But you’ve barely known her.
Even so, we’ve been through life and death together for countless times.
She risked her life for me.
And I have absolutely no doubt in this love.
How could you be so negligent to your own duty as the crown princess?
Please forgive me, Father.
But I’m afraid I won’t be able to live without her.
Please grant me your approval, Father.
Is she more important to you than Madelin?
Yes.
More than the royal title and all the money you’d gain from it?
No matter what I say, you will still choose this path, won’t you?
Yes.
Fine! I now pronounce Princess Catherine a commoner. She must leave the palace immediately
and shall not take a single valuable item with her!
I’ve arranged a quiet and peaceful place for you to stay.
Thank you for helping me, Karel.
What are you going to do next?
Once I’m able to settle down, I’ll fly to Thailand to see Miss Vayo.
About Father, you don’t need to worry much.
He loves you so dearly. He won’t stay angry for long.
The first snow should be coming soon.
Once everything is over, let’s go see the snow in Madelin together.
It’s our first snow. Are you watching?
Yes, I am.
Is the snow here beautiful like I’ve told you?
Miss Blew.
I mean Princess Catherine. What are you doing here, Your Highness?
You don’t need to use royal terms with me. I’m no longer a princess.
What do you mean?
Father punished me. He removed my royal title
and banished me from the palace.
What have you done? Why is the punishment so serious?
I just told him…that I love you.
Now, I can finally cross the line to be with you…as I promised.
From now on, there’ll be just Lom and Blew–no more Princess.
I love you, Blew.
I love you too, Lom.
When are you going back to Thailand?
At first, I planned to leave after your coronation ceremony was done.
But now, I’ve changed my mind.
I’m going to take you back with me too.
But now that I’m not a princess anymore, will everyone be okay with it?
I’m completely broke. What else can I do if I go to Thailand?
You can make me happy.
Don’t worry, I’ll look after you for the rest of my life.
I never thought this day would come true.
Neither do I. It’s like a dream.
But a beautiful one, isn’t it?
I’m sorry.
I want to make it right first.
You know what I mean, right?
Quite sweet.
Have you heard from Lom, Din?
I’m worried sick about her–
being heartbroken and staying afar from home like that.
If I still can’t get ahold of her, I’m going to report a missing person.
I tried calling but her phone is off. She’s probably trying to hold it together.
Anyway, I’ll tell Fah to ask Prince Karel if he could help.
My dear Lom, she must be crying her heart out right now. Right, Din?
I already sent Princess to where Miss Lom is staying.
Does that mean they are both together now, Your Highness?
Finally, my sister can be happy.
Thanks to you for letting me know beforehand.
Is your name Blew, Sister? You look so beautiful like a princess.
Thank you.
Wind said you’re the person she loves.
You’re Wind’s princess. Wind wants you to join her at breakfast.
Good girl.
Let’s go, Princess.
What’s all this?
These kids just want to know you.
Are you hungry?
Close your eyes first.
Fooling around again?
Please close your eyes.
Thank you.
In my eyes, you’ll always be my princess.
My princess forever.
Please marry me.
I’ll keep you safe for the rest of your life.
I, Vayo Watinwanich, take you, Catherine De Laina Blew, to be my wife.
I promise to stay true to you–to have and to hold, for better or for worse.
I, Catherine De Laina Blew, take you, Vayo Watinwanich, to be my wife.
And to love and respect you, until death do us apart.
Are you nervous?
Just a little.
I thought you said you dated many girls before.
Well, I’m quite reserved when it comes to that thing.
My virtue is well guarded.
I’m keeping it for you only.
Unbelievable.
It’s true.
There’s one thing I want you to know.
Yes?
Whatever is mine…will only be mine.
Then…
Here you go, it’s your favourite.
Three pieces. If you finish them all, you might get diabetes.
I already have it.
I’m home.
Lom! Sweetie!
Why haven’t you reached out to me at all?
Do you know how worried I am?
I’m sorry, Mum.
I have someone I want to introduce to both of you.
What? You want to introduce your girlfriend to us, huh?
Please come in.
Princess!
You don’t need to do that, I’m just Blew–no longer a princess.
What happened?
Why is the princess with you?
You and the princess already got married in Madelin?
Yes, I gave up my royal title and am now a commoner.
I’m no longer a princess.
I’m sorry I haven’t told you earlier.
Please don’t blame her, General Wathit.
Not General Wathit.
You have to call us ‘Dad’ and ‘Mum’.
You want me to call you Dad and Mum?
Yes, that’s right.
You’re my daughter-in-law now, aren’t you?
But still, what you did was wrong.
I can’t accept it.
But Dad, I think you already know that I love Blew.
Yes, I do! Your mum does too.
Who wouldn’t? You threw yourself into danger to protect her like that.
So, what is it that you don’t approve of?
What you did was unacceptable. How could you ignore us parents?
Do you think you’re alone in this world? Are you an orphan or what?
Whatever! I don’t care if you already got married in Madelin.
The wedding must happen here too!
Here?
Princess–I mean, Lady Catherine.
Please call me Blew.
You don’t need to use royal terms with me.
I’m going to arrange a prestigious wedding for you and Lom, Your Highness.
Sorry, I mean–Blew.
Thank you–Oh…
Thank you, Dad and Mum.
I’m so happy. Can you please say it again?
Dad, do it too.
Okay, that’s cute.
I’m terribly sorry I won’t be able to attend your wedding due to an urgent duty which requires my attention.
This is a gift that Father would like to give to you.
I think his anger has subsided by now.
I truly wish you happiness in life.
And I do hope we shall meet again soon.
Father and I will always be waiting for your return.
Cheers!
Is it good?
Hiyah!
Geez!
Can you please stop smiling?
Isn’t this your second time getting married?
Those who’ve never been in love would never understand, right, Din?
True that. I also got married twice but I wasn’t as bad as you though.
Well, I’m happy.
Last night, I couldn’t lie on my side or else my happiness might be dripping out of my ears.
You’re having it bad, huh?
What’s so good about love? I don’t get it. It’s nonsense.
Love isn’t something nonsense, Fai.
It’s the other way round. I think love makes us see the true meaning in life
and makes us happier than when all we did in life was work. Trust me.
That’s right. When I lost my parents, I also lost the meaning in life–until I met Rose.
She’s the reason I want to stay alive.
Stop bragging about your wives, Sis.
It’s Blew and my wedding today.
You guys are the same.
The more I hear it, the more I want to puke.
I’d rather stay single for the rest of my life–be an auntie who pampers her nieces and nephews.
Go on.
Hey, where are you going?
What’s wrong with her?
Our Young Master, will she ever get married?
Fat chance, I guess.
Love is something she hates to her guts.
But who knows.
If she happens to find a good love, I don’t think she’ll be able to deny it.
I hope so.
Come.
You sure take time to dress up.
Yeah, two hours.
- Wow.
- I knew it.
Picking what shoes to wear.
You too, honey.
I might be quite talkative today since I hardly get to talk when I’m home.
My wife’s the one who does the talking. Lom probably knows it best.
As parents, we’re so glad to welcome another daughter to our family.
You two have been through a lot before you’d be standing here today.
We want nothing but for you both to always love each other and be a happy family.
At least, love each other like we do.
I’ll let your mother speak too. I’m so happy I got to talk a lot today.
It’s your turn now.
Welcome to our family, dear. That’s it. Thank you.
Thank you, Mum.
I wish you both an everlasting love and happiness.
Finally, it’s Miss Blew who has made our wind stop blowing.
Love each other for a long time.
First, I’d like to say–Congratulations, Miss Blew.
Welcome to the Watinwanich family.
Finally, this tiger has now become toothless.
I’m so happy that you no longer have to walk alone–you’ll always have Miss Blew by your side.
From now on, no matter what happens, don’t ever let go of each other’s hands.
It’s not easy at all for you to finally be together today.
Please remember and cherish these moments for as long as you can.
Welcome to the Watinwanich family, Miss Blew.
Thank you.
Congratulations to both of you.
See? I told you it’s risky but it’s worth giving it a try.
And here you are. Well done, Bro.
Right, thank you so much, everyone.
All of you here means a lot to me
Most of all, thank you for loving me, Blew.
I promise to love, cherish, and care for you more than my own life.
Thank you everyone too.
Thank you for all the love and warmth you’ve given to both of us.
And thank you for making me realise what it’s like to love someone more than your own life.
I love you.
Throw it to me, Miss Blew! I wanna be taken! Throw it here, quick! I want to be in love!
Throw it to me!
Throw it to me! I want to be in love!
Surprise! It’s for you.
Yes?
I hope you’ll find your true love soon.
Fai, we’re looking forward to welcoming our youngest sister-in-law.
Aww, you’ll definitely get yourself a girlfriend.
Anyone want it?
Do you want it? Do you?
Finally, we can be Wind and Phatpha once again.
Says who? It’s actually Lom and Blew. We don’t need to disguise ourselves anymore.
I can’t believe the princess of Madelin is now walking right by my side.
Have you ever thought what brought us together when we were actually a world apart?
Thanks to those traitors, maybe.
No, not them.
Then, thanks to the wind for bringing us together.
I love you, Blew.
I love you too, Lom.
♫ I wonder which star it is that guided me to meet you ♫
♫Or is it destiny that has brought us together♫
♫You’re like the wind, carrying me to the sky♫
♫No matter how high, I won’t be afraid♫
♫ Only you is enough, I don’t need anything else ♫
♫ust us together is enough, you’re the meaning in my life♫
♫Every day from now, please stay by my side♫
[Desires in the Wind]
♫and we’ll always have each other♫
[North Star Entertainment]